

Gurunath Shankar Kadu

Software Developer

kadugurunath@gmai

7208209940

7 Years 0 Month

Experienced and proficient in Software Development, javascript, html, microsoft azure, jquery, css, sql, react. js, ajax, rest, jenkin, node. js, linux, mysql, aws, ,docker, mongodb, typescript, web services, bootstrap, json, express, elastic search, graphql

Profile Summary

With over 7 years of experience in various roles such as Team Lead, Technical Consultant, Node JS Developer, and Solution Developer, I have honed my skills in a wide range of technologies including Angular JS, Node JS, JavaScript, RabbitMQ, ElasticSearch, MongoDB, MSSQL, PostGre, and MYSQL. I have led teams and worked on projects for major clients such as Microsoft and Google. My experience includes developing Partner Parts Order and Claim and Warranty Check modules, creating and consuming web services, and providing production deployment support. I have also developed new microservices for handling notifications, wishlists, and error detection. My proficiency extends to third-party integration APIs and developing test cases for different modules.

Education

2016, Full Time

PG Diploma, Mumbai University,

2015, Full Time

B.Tech/B.E., Shivaji rao s jondhale college of engineering, 78%

2008

10th, Maharashtra, Marathi, 75-79.9%

Work Experience

2023 - Present

Software Developer

Synechron

Developed different services integration like pdf generation, email, WhatsApp SMS. Made a third party integration API. Created and modified pdf templates using EJS. Wrote test cases for different modules. Third party intergration

2021 - 2023

Technical consultant

Xebia

Developed new Microservices for handling EMI life Cycle, Do not call, Update Name, Non-closure loan, family banking etc. Made third Party Integration APIs like (Finacle, fin one), Aadhar etc.

2019 - 2021

Node JS developer

Myglamm

Developed new Microservices for handling Notification (SMS, Email, Whatsapp), Wishlist etc. Made third Party Integration APIs. Made a checker MS which found Errors/bugs in the system and assigned it to dedicated Developers.

2019 - 2019

Senior Analytics (technical Solutions)

Hansa Cequity solutions Pvt Ltd

Developed loyality programme for mahindra.

2016 - 2019

Solution Developer

B2x service solutions Pvt Ltd

Developed Partner onboarding module as per request and same as Salesforce module. Changes in the Salesforce module should reflect in the partner onboarding Module.

Projects

1495 Days

myglamm

Developed New Microservices for handling Notification (SMS, Email, Whatsapp), Wishlist etc. Made third Party Integration APIs. Made a checker MS which found Errorsbugs in the system and assigned it to dedicated Developers.

214 Days

purple Club Loyalty Program

it's loyalty program for enrollment customer, assign offers, maintain points of loyalty program

334 Days

Esp

Developed Enterprise Service module for transaction. Consumed different web services as per requirement.

365 Days

Partner Portal

partner portal is used to to on board partner data.to perform warranty claim, part order system

Courses & Certifications

Cdac

PG-DAC

Software Development		nt javascrip	ot an	ngular js java		html	micros	oft azure	•
jquery	css sq	ıl react.js	ajax	rest	jenkin	node	.js lir	nux n	nysql
aws pl	hp docl	ker mongo	db ty	pescript	web s	ervices	boots	trap j	son
express	elastic se	earch Team	n lead	Technica	l Lead	git	mvc	AWS Lar	nbda

Language

marathi Expert **English** Proficient **hindi** Proficient

Personal Details

Date of Birth

Gender

Marital Status

10th November 1992

Male

Married

Address

ROOM NO.502,OM CHAITNYA VISHNU TOWER,NEAR MEERA HOSPITAL,VALIPEER ROAD,KALYAN (WEST)